LAKSHAN MARTIN

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING STUDENT

PERSONAL PROFILE

Since transitioning careers from Accounting to Software Engineering, I've been able to follow my personal interests in Tech and Creative Development. I hope to further develop my skill-set and supplement my education with industry experience.

EDUCATION

Curtin University
Bachelor of Science
(Computing)
Expected Graduation 2022

Curtin University Bachelor of Commerce (Accounting) 2009 - 2012

CONTACT

- lakshan.martin@gmail.com
- 0433 474 225
- /LakshanMartin
- in <u>/lakshan-martin</u>

/lakshanmartin.netlify.app

SKILLS

- Java, C, MySQL, Python, JavaScript (ReactJS), HTML
- Object Oriented Programming
- Android Development
- Web Development
- Git/GitHub

AWARDS

 Commendation in recognition of High Academic Achievement (Semester 1, 2020)

WORK EXPERIENCE

CoderDojo WA | Student Mentor

JUL 2021 - PRESENT

- Assist students aged 12-17 with their personal and scholarly software projects
- Introduce beginners to the foundations of software programming
- Participate in the management of the CoderDojo program

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Butler Settineri | Intermediate Accountant

MAR 2017 - DEC 2017

Oaktree Accounting | Accountant

AUG 2013 - MAR 2017